

Samaneh Basmehchi

Frontend Developer

About me

A software engineer with 6+ years of experience in frontend development.

A clean coder who has excellent skills in problem-solving and agile development in eCommerce, payment gateway, map, and admin panel domains.

Contact Details

Email: samanehbasmechi@gmail.com

LinkedIn: samaneh-basmechi

GitHub: samaneh-basmechi

Location: Tehran, Iran

Education

Shahroud University of Technology

Bachelor's degree-Computer software engineering 2014-2018

Mohajer Iravani High School

Math. & Physics-diploma certificate 2012-2014

Motahari High School

Math. & Physics 2010-2012

Skills

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Sass, Scss
- TypeScript
- JavaScript
- Angular 2+
- RxJS
- WebSocket
- PWA
- Git/Git Flow
- OOP

Familiar with

- Unit Testing
- React JS
- Next JS
- Node JS
- Express JS
- Photoshop
- Docker
- Hosting
- C
- PHP
- NgRx
- Linux

Work Experience

Digikala/Digipay - Frontend Developer

June 2021 - Present

• Develop 3 projects of payment using angular 2+ and clean code principles in an agile team and Linux environment

Address Click - Angular Team Lead

Dec 2020 - June 2021

- Developed audit panel using Angular 11, chart JS, Angular Material, ng2-Jalali, and Sass libraries.
- Participated in eCommerce website using React JS and Next JS.

Dade Kavan Apadana - Frontend Developer

Apr 2020 - Dec 2020

- Developed Iran Mall admin panel using Angular 10 with dark/light themes,
 Mapbox, chart JS, ng2-Jalali, ngx-image-cropper, web socket, and Sass libraries.
- Developed dkap.ir as PWA website (multilingual) using Angular 10, Scully, Sass, and ngx-translate libraries.

Carpino- Frontend Developer

Agu 2019 - Apr 2020

Developed the company admin panel using Angular 9, Angular Material,
 WebSocket, ng2-Jalali, Datatables.net, Mapbox, and Sass libraries.

Alo Ostad - Frontend Developer

Oct 2018 - Sep 2019

- Developed the company admin panel using Angular 6, primeNG, ng2-Jalali, and Sass libraries.
- Improved load performance of admin panel by 1000%

Freelance - Frontend Developer

Jan 2015 - Oct 2020

- Developed prototype of Equestrian Federation (multilingual) using Angular 2+, nax-translate, and Sass libraries.
- Developed prototype of Educational site (multilingual) using Angular 2+, MDB, ngx-translate, and Sass libraries.
- Developed MegaBourse website (personal project) as PWA using Angular 2+,
 Scully, ng2-Jalali, Angular Material, and Sass libraries.